<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE><LABEL name="CCPayments">Credit Card Payments Processed</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="InFile">in file</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CKPayments">Electronic Check Payments Processed</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PaymentsText">RECURRING PAYMENTS: Click the "Create New Payments" button to create a payment for each Sales Item 
	that is recurring and has a due date on or before the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Thru">Thru</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CCCKText">PAYMENT FILES: Click the "Create Payment Files" button to create a batch file of all new 
	payments to be processed. Click the "Mark Payments Pending" to change the status of these same payments to pending.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UpdateCCCKText">PAYMENT STATUS: Click the "Update Payments Status" to upload a status file for previously processed payments and update their status.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CommissionsText">COMMISSIONS: Click the "Create Commissions" button to create the specified type of 
	commissions for all approved payments that have not yet been commissioned and thier payment date is less than or 
	equal to the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PayoutsText">PAYOUTS: Click the "Create Payouts" button to create a summary of all commissions recently created 
	on or before the specified date for each person that has earned commissions.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="For">For</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="DebitsText">DEBITS: Click the "Create Debits" button to create debits against unpaid payouts
	 for recurring payments coming due within one month from the specified date below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PayoutFileText">PAYOUT FILE: Click the "Create Payout File" button to create a payout file of all 
	unpaid payouts with a minimum amount specified below and to be paid on the specified date below. Click the "Mark 
	Payouts Paid" button to set the status to paid and the paid date to the specified date below for the same payouts 
	in the payout file.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Min">Minimum $</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="On">On</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SetPaidDate">Set Paid Date to</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Accounting">Accounting</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmCreateSOPayments">Are you sure you want to Create New Payments for all recurring sales orders?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmCreateMEPayments">Are you sure you want to Create New Payments for all due members?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmCreateCCCKFiles">Are you sure you want to Create payment processing files from all payments with a "Submitted" Status?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmSetCCCKPending">Are you sure you want to Update "Submitted" payments to "Pending" Status?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmCreateCommissions">Are you sure you want to Create New Commissions for all Approved Payments?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmCreatePayouts">Are you sure you want to Create New Payouts for all unpaid Commissions?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmDebits">Are you sure you want to Create Debits from earned commissions for upcoming recurring payments?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmPayoutFile">Are you sure you want to Create a Payout File of all payouts to be paid on the specified date and equal to or greater than the specified amount?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ConfirmUpdatePayouts">Are you sure you want to set the status to paid and the paid date to the specified date for all unpaid payouts?</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreateSOPayments">Create New Sales Order Payments</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreateMEPayments">Create New Member Payments</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreateCCCKFiles">Create Payment Files</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SetCCCKPending">Mark Payments Pending</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UpdateStatus">Update Payments Status</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreateCommissions">Create Commissions</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreatePayouts">Create Payouts</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreateDebits">Create Debits</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PayoutFile">Create Payout File</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UpdatePayouts">Mark Payouts Paid</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Return">Return</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
