<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE><LABEL name="NotAvailable">Oops! The selected function is not currently available.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="BillingTokens">CREATE BILLING TOKENS: Click the "Process" button below to create billing token for new members.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreatePayments">CREATE PAYMENTS: Click the "Process" button below to create payments for members due to be billed on or before the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PaymentFile">PROCESS PAYMENTS: Click the "Process" button below to process payments with a submitted status.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="DeclinedTokens">LIST DECLINED TOKENS: Click the "Process" button below to view a list of members with declined tokens.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="DeclinedPayments">LIST DECLINED PAYMENTS: Click the "Process" button below to view a list of members with declined payments.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UpdateDeclined">UPDATE DECLINED PAYMENTS: Click the "Process" button below to update declined payments with recently provided billing info.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="BonusQualified">VERIFY BONUS QUALIFIED MEMBERS: Click the "Process" button below to calculate all active 
	members that are qualified to earn bonuses or that are "Qualify" locked after the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CalcBonuses">CALCULATE BONUSES: Click the "Process" button below to calculate commissions and bonuses 
	for all member payments in the specified date range below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="DisplayBonuses">UNHIDE NEW BONUSES: Click the "Process" button below to display all hidden new commissions and bonuses.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreatePayouts">CREATE PAYOUTS: Click the "Process" button below to create payouts for all unpaid 
	bonuses up to the date specified below and totaling $40+ per member.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PaymentCredits">CREAT PAYMENT CREDITS: Click the "Process" button below to create payment credits 
	for all members with bill dates due within the next 7 days that have sufficient earned bonuses that have not been paid yet.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PayoutQualified">VERIFY QUALIFIED BONUS CHECKS: Click the "Process" button below to calculate all active 
	members that are qualified to receive a bonus check.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PayoutFile">CREATE PAYOUT FILE: Click the "Process" button below to create payout files 
	stored in the "Payouts" folder, for ACH transactions and paper check printing. 
	Pending payouts will be processed up to the date specified below and totaling $40+ per member.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PayoutPaid">MARK PENDING PAYOUTS PAID: Click the "Process" button below to update the status of all 
	pending payouts to paid, up to the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="DisplayPayouts">UNHIDE NEW PAYOUTS: Click the "Process" button below to display all hidden new payouts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MaintainSales">RECALCULATE GROUP SALES VOLUME: Click the "Process" button below to recalculate all group sales volume and check for new promotions.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MaintainSummary">POST SALES SUMMARY: Click the "Process" button below to post the current personal and group sales volume for all active Resellers and Affiliates with personal sales volume. The sales summary will be posted with the date below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ListOrphans">LIST ORPHANED AFFILIATES: Click the "Process" button below to view a list of affiliates without active sponsors.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreateWallets">CREATE NEW eWALLETS: Click the "Process" button below to list all eWallets for all new active International affiliates to be imported into iPayout.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="AssignWallets">ASSIGN NEW eWALLETS: Click the "Process" button below to setup the Payout Method to eWallet for all new active International affiliates.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SetAlerts">SET MEMBER ALERTS: Click the "Process" button below to set declined payment and no backup alerts for all members.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CleanupData">CLEANUP OLD DATA: Click the "Process" button below to delete incomplete enrollments and other old data.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="From">From</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="To">To</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="eWalletHdr">UserName,FirstName,LastName,CompanyName,Address1,Address2,City,State,ZipCode,Country2xFormat,PhoneNumber,CellPhoneNumber,EmailAddress,SSN,CompanyTaxID,GovernmentID,MilitaryID,PassportNumber,DriversLicense,DateOfBirth,WebsitePassword,DefaultCurrency,PreferredLanguage</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Process">Process</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Close">Close</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
