<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE><LABEL name="TrackerReports">Activity Reports</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TrackMeter">Success Track</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ActivitySummary">Activity Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PersonalSummary">Personal Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="LeadershipSummary">Leadership Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PersonalProgress">Personal Progress</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="LeadershipProgress">Leadership Progress</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalPersonalResults">Goal Personal Results</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalPersonalActivities">Goal Personal Activities</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalLeadershipResults">Goal Leadership Results</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalLeadershipActivities">Goal Leadership Activities</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalTotalPoints">Goal Total Points</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamTracks">Team Tracks</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamActivitySummary">Team Activity Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamPersonalSummary">Team Personal Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamLeadershipSummary">Team Leadership Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamPersonalProgress">Team Personal Progress</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamLeadershipProgress">Team Leadership Progress</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemTracks">System Tracks</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemActivitySummary">System Activity Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemPersonalSummary">System Personal Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemLeadershipSummary">System Leadership Summary</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemPersonalProgress">System Personal Progress</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemLeadershipProgress">System Leadership Progress</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="For">For</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Membership">Total Days</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Prev7">Last 7 Days</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Prev30">Last 30 Days</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="WeekToDate">This Week</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MonthToDate">This Month</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="YearToDate">This Year</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PrevWeek">Previous Week</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PrevMonth">Previous Month</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PrevYear">Previous Year</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="From">From</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="To">To</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NoReportData">No Data for the Selected Report!</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ResultsText">of your points come from Key Results</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ActivitiesText">of your points come from Regular Activities</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="RatioText">Your ratio of Key Results to Regular Activities is</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Daily">Daily</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Weekly">Weekly</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Monthly">Monthly</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Quarterly">Quarterly</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TrackMeterText">The Succeess Track shows you where you are on your track to success. Change the time period to see how you've done for that specific date range.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ActivitySummaryText">The Activity Summary displays the percentage of your work that is from personal activities and results, and leadership activities and results you've done 
	for your team.  Initially you will have more emphasis on personal activities and results with a shift to leadership activities and results as your team matures.  You should also see 
	a good balance of activities and results. The ratio at the top indicated how much activity is need to produce results. For example; a 25% ratio means you generated 4 activity points to produce each result point.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PersonalSummaryText">The Personal Summary displays a list of personal activities with the highest points at the top of the list.  This displays both activities and results.  
	Results are preceded with **.  This will give you a good idea of where you are spending your personal efforts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="LeadershipSummaryText">The Leadership Summary displays a list of leadership activities with the highest points at the top of the list.  This displays both activities and results.
		Results are preceded with **.  This will give you a good idea of where you are spending your leadership efforts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PersonalProgressText">The Personal Progress displays a time line of all personal activities and results.  Your activities (green) and results (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of your progress to see if your efforts are increasing or declining.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="LeadershipProgressText">The Leadersghip Progress displays a time line of all leadership activities and results.  Your activities (green) and results (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of your progress to see if your efforts are increasing or declining.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemTracksText">The System Tracks show you how many and what percentage of your members are on each of the five tracks for the specified time period.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemActivitySummaryText">The System Activity Summary displays the percentage of your work that is from your member's personal activities and results, and from their 
	leadership activities and results.  Initially you're System will have more emphasis on personal activities and results with a shift to leadership activities and results as your System matures.  You should also see
		a good balance of activities and results. The ratio at the top indicated how much activity is need to produce results. For example; a 25% ratio means you're System generated 4 activity points to produce each result point.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemPersonalSummaryText">The System Personal Summary displays a list of your System's personal activities with the highest points at the top of the list.  This displays both activities and results.
		Results are preceded with **.  This will give you a good idea of where you're System is spending their personal efforts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemLeadershipSummaryText">The System Leadership Summary displays a list of your System's leadership activities with the highest points at the top of the list.  This displays both activities and results.
		Results are preceded with **.  This will give you a good idea of where you're System is spending their leadership efforts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemPersonalProgressText">The System Personal Progress displays a time line of all your System's personal activities and results.  Your System's activities (green) and results (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of your System's progress to see if their efforts are increasing or declining.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SystemLeadershipProgressText">The System Leadersghip Progress displays a time line of all your System's leadership activities and results.  Your System's activities (green) and results (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of your System's progress to see if their efforts are increasing or declining.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamTracksText">The Team Tracks show you how many and what percentage of your team members are on each of the five tracks for the specified time period.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamActivitySummaryText">The Team Activity Summary displays the percentage of your work that is from your team member's personal activities and results, and from their
		leadership activities and results.  Initially you're Team will have more emphasis on personal activities and results with a shift to leadership activities and results as your Team matures.  You should also see
		a good balance of activities and results. The ratio at the top indicated how much activity is need to produce results. For example; a 25% ratio means you're Team generated 4 activity points to produce each result point.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamPersonalSummaryText">The Team Personal Summary displays a list of your Team's personal activities with the highest points at the top of the list.  This displays both activities and results.
		Results are preceded with **.  This will give you a good idea of where you're Team is spending their personal efforts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamLeadershipSummaryText">The Team Leadership Summary displays a list of your Team's leadership activities with the highest points at the top of the list.  This displays both activities and results.
		Results are preceded with **.  This will give you a good idea of where you're Team is spending their leadership efforts.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamPersonalProgressText">The Team Personal Progress displays a time line of all your Team's personal activities and results.  Your Team's activities (green) and results (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of your Team's progress to see if their efforts are increasing or declining.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TeamLeadershipProgressText">The Team Leadersghip Progress displays a time line of all your Team's leadership activities and results.  Your Team's activities (green) and results (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of your Team's progress to see if their efforts are increasing or declining.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalPersonalResultsText">The Goal Personal Results Report displays a time line of your defined goals and your actual points for all personal results.  Your actual points (green) and your projected goal points (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of how you have performed compared to your projected goals.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalPersonalActivitiesText">The Goal Personal Activities Report displays a time line of your defined goals and your actual points for all personal activities.  Your actual points (green) and your projected goal points (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of how you have performed compared to your projected goals.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalLeadershipResultsText">The Goal Leadership Results Report displays a time line of your defined goals and your actual points for all leadership results.  Your actual points (green) and your projected goal points (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of how you have performed compared to your projected goals.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalLeadershipActivitiesText">The Goal Leadership Activities Report displays a time line of your defined goals and your actual points for all leadership activities.  Your actual points (green) and your projected goal points (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of how you have performed compared to your projected goals.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GoalTotalPointsText">The Goal Total Points Report displays a time line of your defined goals and your actual points for all personal and leadership results and activities.  Your actual points (green) and your projected goal points (red) are displayed on separate lines.
		This will give you a good idea of how you have performed compared to your projected goals.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Report">Report</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="View">View</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Close">Close</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
