<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE><LABEL name="CalcEnrollment">CALCULATE ENROLLMENT BONUSES: Click the "Process" button below to create enrollment bonuses for all new student payments in the specified date range below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CalcTuition">CALCULATE TUITION BONUSES: Click the "Process" button below to create tuition bonuses for all monthly student payments in the specified date range below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CreatePayouts">CREATE PAYOUTS: Click the "Process" button below to create payouts for all unpaid bonuses up to the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PaidPayouts">MARK PENDING PAYOUTS PAID: Click the "Process" button below to update the status of all pending payouts to paid, up to the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CalcReferrals">CALCULATE REFERRALS: Click the "Process" button below to calculate all member's personal and team referrals.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CalcAdvancement">CALCULATE ADVANCEMENT: Click the "Process" button below to calculate advancements. Confirm that the referrals are current with the "Calculate Referrals" process.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PostReferrals">POST MONTHLY REFERRALS: Click the "Process" button below to post all member's currrent personal and team referrals with the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="QualifyMembers">CALCULATE QUALIFIED MEMBERS: Click the "Process" button below to calculate all active members that are qualified to receive bonuses or that are "Qualify" locked after the date specified below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ExportPayouts">EXPORT PENDING PAYOUTS: Click the "Process" button below to create payout files 
	stored in the "Payouts" folder, for ACH transactions and paper check printing. 
	Pending payouts will be processed up to the date specified below and totaling $50+ per member.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PaymentCredits">CREAT PAYMENT CREDITS: Click the "Process" button below to create payment credits 
	for all members with bill dates due within the next 30 days that have sufficient earned commissions
	that have not been paid yet.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CalcFastStart">CALCULATE FAST START BONUSES: Click the "Process" button below to create Fast Start bonuses for all new students with their first month ending in the specified date range below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CalcLeadership">CALCULATE LEADERSHIP BONUSES: Click the "Process" button below to create leadership bonuses for all monthly student payments in the specified date range below.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="From">From</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="To">To</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Process">Process</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Close">Close</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
