<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE>
	<LABEL name="-2147220493">Oops, value not within the allowable range for </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220492">Oops, too large a value entered for </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220491">Oops, too small a value entered for </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220490">Oops, entry is required for </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220489">Oops, invalid characters entered for </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220488">Oops, too many characters entered for </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220487">Oops, not enough characters entered for </LABEL>

	<LABEL name="-2147220480">Oops, Input Name Not Specified!</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220479">Oops, Input Name Not Found!</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220478">Oops, No File Sent!</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220477">Oops, File Length Too Long! </LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220476">Oops, Empty File Extension Not Allowed!</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220475">Oops, EXE File Extension Not Allowed!</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220474">Oops, Invalid File Extension!</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="-2147220503">Oops, You cannot change the previous notes.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220504">Oops, either your logon ID or password is incorrect.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220505">Oops, the logon ID you entered has been disabled.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220506">Oops, New Logon and Confirm Logon do not match. Please re-enter the Confirm Logon to continue.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220507">Oops, Change logon failed. The old logon is not correct.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220508">Oops, New Password and Confirm Password do not match. Please re-enter the Confirm Password to continue.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220509">Oops, New Password and Password match. Please re-enter a New Password to continue.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220510">Oops, Change password failed. The old password is not correct.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220511">Oops, Reset password failed. Can not locate user.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220512">Oops, Could not find the Email address. Please re-enter.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220513">Oops, The Logon/Website Name is not available. Please select another or contact Member Support for assistance.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220514">Oops, Your access to the system has been limited - Access Denied.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220515">Oops, Your access to the system has been disallowed - IP Address Denied.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220516">Oops, Your access to the system has been disallowed - Too Many IP Addresses.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220517">Oops, Please contact Customer Support to access the system.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220518">Oops, Please select a Lead Page to email to the new prospects.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220519">Oops, Please enter a new prospect first name.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220520">Oops, Please enter a new prospect last name.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220521">Oops, Please enter a valid new prospect email address.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220522">Oops, Please answer 5 or more questions.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147220523">Oops, Please select a Presentation to email to the new prospects.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="-2147217873">Oops, Logon Name is registered to another user.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="-2147217874">Oops, Logon Name is registered to another company.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10001">Oops, Please select a product to purchase.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10002">Oops, Please select the Product modify link to enter required options.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10003">Oops, Please enter a Recurring Product Code for the Recurring Amount.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10004">Oops, Please enter text to search for.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10005">Oops, Full Address is Required.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10006">Oops, Phone Number is Required.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10011">Oops, Identification Number is Required.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10014">Oops, Invalid Check Routing Number or Account Number.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10007">Oops, Invalid Check Routing Number.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10008">Oops, Invalid Length of Credit Card Number.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10009">Oops, Invalid Credit Card Number.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10010">Oops, Selected Card Type does not match Card Number.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10012">Oops, Invalid Credit Card Type.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10013">Oops, Credit Card date has expired.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10015">Oops, Invalid Promotion Code.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10016">Oops, The Promotion has not started yet.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10017">Oops, The Promotion has expired.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10018">Oops, The Promotion has been used.</LABEL>
	
	<LABEL name="10101">Oops, Your Logon Name must be at least six characters/numbers long.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10102">Oops, Your Password must be at least six characters/numbers long.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10103">Oops, You must agree to the terms and conditions.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10104">Oops, Email Address Already Exists.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10105">Oops, Your Trial Membership has expired.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10106">Oops, Your System is not available.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10107">Oops, The system is not accepting new members at this time.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10110">Oops, The Next Question cannot be specified by the choice for multi-selection.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10111">Oops, You have exceeded the maximum number of allowed active members.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10112">Oops, The selected feature is not available with your membership. Please review the available upgrade options.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10113">Oops, The selected Mentor # does not exist.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10114">Oops, The selected Mentor is not able to be a Mentor with their current membership.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10115">Oops, Specify the date range to process.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10116">Oops, Please specify who referred you.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10117">Oops, The payment is too small to payoff the debt.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10118">Oops, You must agree to be billed by Pinnacle Systems.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10119">Oops, Product out of stock for specified quantity.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10120">Oops, Missing Custom Field for Inventory Attribute.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10121">Oops, Downline member not found. Be more specific.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10122">Oops, Invalid Email Address.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10123">Oops, This email address is already assigned to someone else.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10124">Oops, Please enter at least 6 characters for the Password.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10125">Oops, Please enter a First Name.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10126">Oops, Please enter a Last Name.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10127">Oops, Please enter a Company Name.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10128">Oops, You must agree to the payment terms.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10129">Oops, The Email Address could not be found.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10130">Oops, Your password is incorrect.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10131">Oops, Please enter at least one personal computer.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10132">Oops, Please enter your name, email and phone.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10133">Oops, Please enter the required information.</LABEL>

	<LABEL name="10134">Oops, The Phone Number could not be found.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10135">Oops, The Account Number could not be found.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="10136">Oops, This Phone Number is already assigned to someone else. Try adding your country code as a prefix.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10137">Oops, The Username could not be found.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10138">Oops, Invalid Security Code.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10139">Oops, Please enter an amount greater than zero.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10140">Oops, Please enter a valid GCR Coin Address.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10141">Oops, PIN Code is already used by another staff member.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10142">Oops, Invalid PIN Code.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10143">Oops, Please enter the Shopper Password to redeem points.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10144">Oops, The Shopper Password is Invalid.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10145">Oops, The reward points value is less than the total amount.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10146">Oops, Not enough special award points for the selected award.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10147">Oops, Please enter a sales Ticket Number.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10148">Oops, Please enter a positive value for the total and net amounts.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10149">Oops, Please enter a shopper phone number or email.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10150">Oops, Please enter your numeric PIN Code.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10151">Oops, Please enter numbers only for your PIN Code.</LABEL>

  <LABEL name="10152">Oops, Please enter an amount greater than zero to transfer.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10153">Oops, Please enter an amount less or equal to the total points available.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10154">Oops, The Shopper could not be found.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10155">Oops, Invalid Customer #.</LABEL>
  <LABEL name="10156">Oops, The Shopper Account is Inactive. Contact support@NexxusRewards.com</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
