<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE><LABEL name="HomeTax">HomeTax</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="HomeTaxs">HomeTaxs</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NewHomeTax">NewHomeTax</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="FindHomeTax">FindHomeTax</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="HomeTaxID">HomeTax</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MemberID">Member</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate">Tax Bracket</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Office">Office Percentage</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Miles">Business Miles</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Home">Home</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Meetings">Meeting Expenses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Meals">Business Meals</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Supplies">Business Supplies</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Gifts">Business Gifts</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Materials">Marketing Materials</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Phones">Phone Expenses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Internet">Internet Expenses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Kids">Kids Expenses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Subscriptions">Subscriptions</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Entertainment">Entertainment</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Activities">Activities</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Events">Events</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Medical">Medical Expenses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Recreational">Recreational</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate1">10%</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate2">15%</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate3">25%</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate4">28%</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate5">33%</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRate6">35%</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TotalDeductions">You will have a total business tax deduction of</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TotalSavings">Your total annual tax savings will be</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MonthlySavings">Your total monthly savings will be</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="OfficeText">Enter the percentage of your home that you use regularly and exclusively for business 
	purposes. Divide your office space square footage by the total square feet.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="HomeText">Enter your monthly home expenses including mortgage interest, rent, utilities, insurance, security 
	system, real estate taxes, depreciation, maintenance, repairs, painting, and other related costs.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MilesText">Enter the monthly number of miles you and your spouse drive for business purposes.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MeetingsText">Enter the estimated monthly average cost of business meeting expenses including airfare, hotel, 
	parking, and other related travel and meeting expenses.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MealsText">Enter the monthly cost of business meals (estimate the number of business meals - breakfast, 
	lunch and dinner - you think you might eat)</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SuppliesText">Enter the monthly cost of office supplies including paper, printer cartridges, postage, envelopes, copies, etc.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MaterialsText">Enter the monthly cost of marketing materials including business cards, leads, flyers, advertising in print, radio, internet and other forms of marketing.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="PhonesText">Enter the monthly cost of your business phone line and you and your spouse's cell phones and other electronic devices.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="InternetText">Enter the monthly cost of your Internet access.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="MedicalText">Enter the monthly average cost of your current medical related costs including health insurance, 
	out-of-pocket health care expenses for your family, such as co-payments, deductibles, or drug costs not covered by 
	insurance, dental expenses, braces, vision expenses, eye care, contacts, glasses, etc.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SubscriptionsText">Enter the monthly average cost of purchased newspapers, magazines, books and on-line media.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="EntertainmentText">Enter the monthly average cost of entertaining friends and family members in your home.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ActivitiesText">Enter the monthly average cost of going out to the movies, sporting events, hunting, fishing, or other similar activities.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="EventsText">Enter the monthly average cost of season tickets to sporting events, Broadway plays, or other events.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="RecreationalText">Enter the monthly cost of your boat, camper, motor home or other recreational vehicles. 
	Estimate your operating expenses including park or parking fees, annual maintenance costs, fuel costs, etc.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="KidsText">Enter the monthly amount that you spend on all of your children from ages 6 to 18 including spending money, 
	sport and team fees, camps, eating out including school lunches, trips to the mall, etc. These are all expenses above the amount you pay for normal support such as housing and meals at home.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="GiftsText">Enter the monthly cost of business gifts (maximum is $25 per person annually).</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TaxRateText">Select the tax bracket for which you are currently paying taxes.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="HomeExp">Home Expenses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="mTotalDeductions">Tax Deduction</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="mTotalSavings">Annual Savings</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="mMonthlySavings">Monthly Savings</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Calculate">Calculate</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
