<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1252'?>
<LANGUAGE><LABEL name="Trainer">Trainer</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Trainers">Trainers</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NewTrainer">Trainer Registration</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="FindTrainer">Trainers</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TrainerID">Trainer #</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="AuthUserID">AuthUser</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SponsorID">Sponsor</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UserGroup">User Group</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UserStatus">User Status</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="SponsorName">Sponsor</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="CompanyName">Company Name</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NameLast">Last Name</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NameFirst">First Name</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TrainerName">Contact</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Email">Email</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Street">Street</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Unit">Unit</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="City">City</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="State">State</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Zip">Zip</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Country">Country</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Phone1">Day Phone</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Phone2">Night Phone</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Fax">Mobile Phone</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Status">Status</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Tier">Tier</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Website">Website</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="URL">Affiliate Link</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Image">Image</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="EnrollDate">Enrollment Date</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NewLogon">Logon Name</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NewPassword">Password</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Active">Active</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="InActive">Inactive</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ReadOnly">Read Only</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Pending">Pending</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Tier1">Tier 1</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Tier2">Tier 2</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Tier3">Tier 3</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="TrainerFindText">Select your trainers from the list below.  You can search for your trainers by entering their company name, contact name, or Tier # in the Find text box below and clicking the "Go" button. 20 trainers are displayed at a time. Click the "Previous Page" or "Next Page" links to view additional trainers.  New trainers can be added by clicking the "Trainer Registration" link in the upper right hand corner of this page.
	Select the "Courses" link on each Trainer to edit the courses.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Courses">Courses</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NewTrainerText">CONTACT INFORMATION: Complete the following information to register as a Pinnacle Trainer. You will be emailed your logon name and password to access your secured Trainer Back Office to setup your training course(s). Required fields are indicated with the gold check mark.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="LogonText">LOGON / PASSWORD: Enter a unique Logon name and Password to be used to access your secured Trainer Back Office. If a Logon Name and Password are not entered the system will generate a random Logon and Password and email it to you. Your new Logon name and password will be sent to the email address entered above.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Agree">I have read and agree with these terms and conditions</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Assessments">Assessments</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Attachments">Attachments</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Commissions">Commissions</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Payouts">Payouts</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ResetLogon">ResetLogon</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="EditTrainerText">Edit your contact information below. Scroll down to the bottom of this page to upload a picture of yourself and enter yor description or biography.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="ImageHelp">Click the Upload button to select an image from your personal computer to display 
	on your Trainer information webpage. The image file must be no larger than 15K in size and will be displayed 100 pixels wide.
	Provide your description or biography including optional education, experience, awards, publications, and/or references to be displayed on your trainer information webpage.
	Your description can be professionally formatted with the editor below that has functionality similar to Microsoft Word.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="NoFrameSupport">NoFrameSupport</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="AffiliateLink">To view additional information about our training products and services visit us at</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UploadImageHeader">Upload Image File</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UploadImageText">Click the Browse button to select an image from your personal computer to display on your Trainer information webpage. After you have selected the desired image file, click the Submit button to upload it to the Pinnacle system. The image file must be no larger than 15K in size and will be displayed 100 pixels wide.</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Address">Address</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="UserAccess">User Access</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Description">Description</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Submit">Submit</LABEL>
	<LABEL name="Upload">Upload</LABEL>
</LANGUAGE>
